http://denvergreenchili.com/privacy-policy/

Intro to Roasted Green Chiles
How Hot are Chiles?
January 2009
Privacy Policy Denver Green Chili is committed to maintaining the privacy and protection of your personal information when you visit this website. This policy outlines what information may be collected when you visit the website, and how that information is used. When you continue to visit this website, you are consenting to the practices described in this policy.
DenverGreenChili.com collects information from you when you register on our site. As my readers, we respect your privacy and will take the necessary steps that your critical information will not be misused.
When registering on DenverGreenChili.com or entering giveaways, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on DenverGreenChili.com. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to DenverGreenChili.com’s users based on your visit to DenverGreenChili.com . Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
Any of the information DenverGreenChili.com collects from you may be used in one of the following ways:
• To improve DenverGreenChili.com
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
• To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
• To send periodic emails
DenverGreenChili.com uses cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.
DenverGreenChili.com does not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist DenverGreenChili.com in operating the website, conducting business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. DenverGreenChili.com may also release your information when it is believed that release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Occasionally, at DenverGreenChili.com’s discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, DenverGreenChili.com seeks to protect the integrity of the site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit DenverGreenChili.com. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp
Online Privacy Policy Only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at http://denvergreenchili.com
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy. We reserve the right to change this privacy policy without notice.
Weekly Recipe
Green Chile
Recipe of the Week
Name:
Email:
You can never have too many chiles hanging around.
Recommended products are all reviewed personally by me; I am an affiliate for some products.
Copyright © 2020 Denver Green Chili - All Rights ReservedPowered by WordPress & Atahualpa
